Guide to the John R. Mott Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Subject Files, Series VIII
  - Biography
    - Mercier, Desire (Box 168, Folder 2847)
    - Millp, Samuel J. (Box 168, Folder 2848)
    - Montgomery, Henry (Box 168, Folder 2849)
    - Moody, Dwight L. (Box 168, Folder 2850)
    - Morgan, J.P. (Box 169, Folder 2851)
    - Mott, Lucretia (Box 169, Folder 2852)
    - Moule, Handley (Box 169, Folder 2853)
    - Muller, George (Box 169, Folder 2854)
    - Murray, Andrew, Sr. (Box 169, Folder 2855)
    - Mussolini, Benito (Box 169, Folder 2856)
    - Neesima, Joseph Hardy (Box 169, Folder 2857)
    - Nehru, Jawaharlal (Box 169, Folder 2858)
    - Czar Nicholas, Czarina Alexandra (Box 169, Folder 2859)
    - Nicolay, Baron Paul (Box 169, Folder 2860)
    - Nightingale, Florence (Box 169, Folder 2861)
    - Nott, Eliphalet (Box 169, Folder 2862)
    - Osler, Sir William (Box 169, Folder 2863)
    - Overtoun, Lord
    - Paget, James (Box 169, Folder 2864)
    - Parker, Joseph (Box 169, Folder 2865)
    - Pasteur, Louis (Box 169, Folder 2866)
    - Peabody, Henry W. (Box 169, Folder 2867)
    - Pearsons, D.K. (Box 169, Folder 2868)
    - Penn, William (Box 169, Folder 2869)
    - Pitkin, Horace Tracy (Box 169, Folder 2870)
    - Suckler, Edward Graf (Box 169, Folder 2871)
    - Radstock, Lord (Box 169, Folder 2872)
    - Rainy, Principal (Box 169, Folder 2873)
    - Ramabai, Pandita (Box 169, Folder 2874)
    - Rauschenbusch, Walter (Box 169, Folder 2875)
    - Reading, Lord (Box 169, Folder 2876)
    - Reynolds, James B. (Box 169, Folder 2877)
    - Rhodes, John Cecil (Box 169, Folder 2878)
    - Riis, Jacob (Box 169, Folder 2879)
    - Rockefeller, John D. (Box 169, Folder 2880)
    - Romanes, George J. (Box 169, Folder 2881)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore (Box 169, Folder 2882)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore (Box 169, Folder 2883)
    - Roots, Logan H. (Box 170, Folder 2884)
    - Ross, G.A. Johnston (Box 170, Folder 2885)
    - Rountree, John Stephenson (Box 170, Folder 2886)
    - Satthianadhan, Samuel (Box 170, Folder 2887)
    - Severance, Louis H. (Box 170, Folder 2888)
    - Shaftsbury, Lord Ashley, Earl of (Box 170, Folder 2889)
    - Simpson, James Y. (Box 170, Folder 2890)
    - Smuts, Jan (Box 170, Folder 2891)
    - Speer, Elliott (Box 170, Folder 2892)
    - Spurgeon, Charles H. (Box 170, Folder 2893)
    - Stock, Eugene (Box 170, Folder 2894)
    - Stokes, James (Box 170, Folder 2895)
    - Studd, J.E. Kynaston (Box 170, Folder 2896)
    - Sun Yat-sen (Box 170, Folder 2897)
    - Sunday, William A. (Box 170, Folder 2898)
    - Tagore, Rabindranath (Box 170, Folder 2899)
    - Talbot, Neville Stuart (Box 170, Folder 2900)
    - Temple, William (Box 170, Folder 2901)
    - Tikhon, Patriarch (Basil Belavin) (Box 170, Folder 2902)
    - Torrey, R.A. (Box 170, Folder 2903)
    - Trumbull, Henry Clay (Box 170, Folder 2904)
    - Tze-hsi, Dowager Empress of China (Box 170, Folder 2905)
    - Wanamaker, John (Box 170, Folder 2906)
    - Wanless, William (Box 170, Folder 2907)
    - Washington, Booker T. (Box 170, Folder 2908)
    - Washington, George (Box 170, Folder 2909)
    - Welch, William Henry (Box 170, Folder 2910)
    - Wesley, John (Box 170, Folder 2911)
    - Wescott, Brooke Foss (Box 170, Folder 2912)
    - White, John Campbell (Box 170, Folder 2913)
    - Whitefield, George (Box 170, Folder 2914)
    - Whittle, D.W. Whyte, Alexander (Box 170, Folder 2915)
    - Willard, Frances E. (Box 170, Folder 2916)
    - Williams, George (Box 170, Folder 2917)
    - Williams, S. Wells
    - Williams, Samuel (Box 170, Folder 2918)
    - Wilson, James Hood (Box 170, Folder 2919)
    - Wilson, Woodid (Box 170, Folder 2920)
    - Wright, Henry B. (Box 170, Folder 2921)
    - Yuasa, Hachiro (Box 170, Folder 2922)
  - Related to Specific Countries or Geographical Areas
    - Africa-General (Box 171, Folder 2923)
    - Asia-General (Box 171, Folder 2924)
    - China-General (Box 171, Folder 2925)
    - China: Education, Literati, Students (Box 171, Folder 2926)
    - China: Evangelism, Missions (Box 171, Folder 2927)
    - China: Evangelism, Missions (Box 171, Folder 2928)
    - China: Politics, History (Box 171, Folder 2929)
    - Congo (Box 171, Folder 2930)
    - Czechoslovakia (Box 171, Folder 2931)
    - Denmark (Box 171, Folder 2932)
    - Europe-General (Box 171, Folder 2933)
    - Finland (Box 172, Folder 2934)
    - Germany (Box 172, Folder 2935)
    - Great Britain (Box 172, Folder 2936)
    - India-Caste, Race (Box 172, Folder 2937)
    - India-Church (Box 172, Folder 2938)
    - India-Cities (Box 172, Folder 2939)
    - India-Domestic Life (Box 172, Folder 2940)
    - India-Education (Box 172, Folder 2941)
    - India-Evangelism (Box 172, Folder 2942)
    - India-General (Box 172, Folder 2943)
    - India-Mass Movements (Box 172, Folder 2944)
    - India-Missions (Box 173, Folder 2945)
    - India-Native Christians (Box 173, Folder 2946)
    - India-Non-violence (Box 173, Folder 2947)
    - India-Politics (Box 173, Folder 2948)
    - India-Relations with Britain, U.S. (Box 173, Folder 2949)
    - India-Rural Life (Box 173, Folder 2950)
    - India-Student Associations., Schools (Box 173, Folder 2951)
    - India-Students, Youth (Box 173, Folder 2952)
    - Italy (Box 173, Folder 2953)
    - Indonesia (Box 173, Folder 2954)
    - Japan-Church, Schools, Christian Movements, Organizations (Box 173, Folder 2955)
    - Japan-Church, Orthodox (Box 173, Folder 2956)
    - Japan-Church, Orthodox (Box 174, Folder 2957)
    - Japan-Culture, History, Polictics (Box 174, Folder 2958)
    - Japan-Evangelism, Missions (Box 174, Folder 2959)
    - Japan-General (Box 174, Folder 2860)
    - Japan-General (Box 174, Folder 2861)
    - Japan-Relations between China and Japan (Box 174, Folder 2862)
    - Korea (Box 174, Folder 2963)
    - Latin America-Church, Ecumenism (Box 174, Folder 2964)
    - Latin America-Education (Box 174, Folder 2965)
    - Latin America-Evangelism, Missions (Box 174, Folder 2966)
    - Latin America-Evangelism, Missions (Box 175, Folder 2967)
    - Latin America-Evangelism, Missions (Box 175, Folder 2968)
    - Latin America-Leadership (Box 175, Folder 2969)
    - Latin America-Politics (Domestic), Economy (Box 175, Folder 2970)
    - Latin America-Politics (International) (Box 175, Folder 2971)
    - Latin America-Student Associations, Schools (Box 175, Folder 2972)
    - Latin America-Students, Youth (Box 175, Folder 2973)
    - Near East-Cities (Box 175, Folder 2974)
    - Near East-Culture, History (Box 175, Folder 2975)
    - Near East-Politics (Box 175, Folder 2976)
    - Near East-Rural Areas, Biblical Sites (Box 175, Folder 2977)
    - Philippines (Box 175, Folder 2978)
    - Poland (Box 175, Folder 2979)
    - Rhodesia (Box 175, Folder 2980)
    - Russia-Art, Music, Literature (Box 176, Folder 2981)
    - Russia-Bolshevism (Box 176, Folder 2982)
    - Russia-General (Box 176, Folder 2983)
    - Russia-Living Church Movement (Box 176, Folder 2984)
    - Russia-Orthodox Church-General (Box 176, Folder 2985)
    - Russia-Orthodox Church- Leadership, clergy (Box 176, Folder 2986)
    - Russia-Orthodox Church-Relations abroad (Box 176, Folder 2987)
    - Russia-Orthodox Church-Theology, spiritual life (Box 176, Folder 2988)
    - Russia-Orthodox Church/State Relations (Box 176, Folder 2989)
    - Russia-Orthodox Church/State Relations (Box 176, Folder 2990)
    - Russia-Political and cultural situation (l904-1913) (Box 177, Folder 2991)
    - Russia-Political and cultural situation (l914-1916) (Box 177, Folder 2992)
    - Russia-Political and cultural situation (l917) (Box 177, Folder 2993)
    - Russia-Political and cultural situation (l918-1920) (Box 177, Folder 2994)
    - Russia-Political and cultural situation (l921-1933) (Box 177, Folder 2995)
    - Russia-Political and cultural situation (l940's) (Box 177, Folder 2996)
    - Russia-Political and cultural situation (l950's) (Box 177, Folder 2997)
    - Russia-Religion (Box 177, Folder 2998)
    - Russia-Revolutionaries (Box 178, Folder 2999)
    - Russia-Students, education (Box 178, Folder 3000)
    - South Africa (Box 178, Folder 3001)
    - Turkey-Cities (Box 178, Folder 3002)
    - Turkey-General (Box 178, Folder 3003)
    - United States-Christianity (Box 178, Folder 3004)
    - United States-Cities, urban life (Box 178, Folder 3005)
    - United States-Ethnic groups, immigration (Box 178, Folder 3006)
    - United States-History, politics (Box 178, Folder 3007)
    - United States-History, politic (Box 178, Folder 3008)
    - United States-National parks, natural phenomena (Box 178, Folder 3009)
    - United States-Eastern Orthodox churches (Box 178, Folder 3010)
    - United States-Relations with Europe (Box 179, Folder 3011)
    - United States-Relations with Great Britain (Box 179, Folder 3012)
    - United States-Relations with Latin America (Box 179, Folder 3013)
    - United States-Relations with Far East (Box 179, Folder 3014)
    - United States-Relations with Japan (Box 179, Folder 3015)
    - United States-Relations with Japan (Box 179, Folder 3016)
    - United States-Relations with Russia (1916-1920) (Box 179, Folder 3017)
    - United States-Relations with Soviet Union (1930-1949) (Box 180, Folder 3018)
    - United States-Relations with Soviet Union (1950's) (Box 180, Folder 3019)
    - United States-Roman Catholicism (Box 180, Folder 3020)
    - United States-Roman Catholicism (Box 180, Folder 3021)
    - United States-Rural life (Box 180, Folder 3022)
    - Yugoslavia (Box 180, Folder 3023)
  - Related to Specific Organizations
    - Agricultural Missions, Inc. (See YDSL HR) (Box 180, Folder 181)
    - Allied Youth, Inc., 1941-1949, n.d. (Box 180, Folder 3024)
    - Church History Deputation to the Orient Peace Union (see: YDSL RG61) Committee on Cooperation in Latin America (see: YDSL RG 31, Series I), 1931-1932 (Box 180, Folder 3025)
    - Committee on the Work of John R. Mott, Inc. Financial material, 1923-1953 (Box 180, Folder 3026)
    - Committee on the Work of John R. Mott, Inc. Meeting minutes, 1929-1942 (Box 180, Folder 3027)
    - Committee on the Work of John R. Mott, Inc. Official papers, 1929-1955 (Box 180, Folder 3028)
    - Cornell University, 1887-1888 (Box 181, Folder 3029)
    - Cornell University Fund raising, 1948-1951, n.d. (Box 181, Folder 3030)
    - Cornell University Miscellaneous, 1870-1905 (Box 181, Folder 3031)
    - Cornell University, 1906-1948, n.d. (Box 181, Folder 3032)
    - Emergency Committee of the Missionary Societies of Great Britain, the U.S., and Canada 1918-1919 Council of Churches of Christ (see: YDSL HR) (Box 181, Folder 3032A)
    - First Methodist Church, Orlando, Florida, 1944-1951 (Box 181, Folder 3033)
    - Hall of Fame-New York University, 1940-1950 (Box 181, Folder 3034)
    - Institute of Social and Religious Research, 1921-1934 (Box 181, Folder 3035)
    - Interchurch World Movement of North America Articles, clippings, 1919-1921 (Box 181, Folder 3036)
    - Interchurch World Movement of North America Foreign Survey Department, 1920 (Box 181, Folder 3037)
    - Interchurch World Movement of North America Letters, minutes, memoranda, 1919 (Box 181, Folder 3038)
    - Interchurch World Movement North America Letters, minutes, memoranda, 1920, n.d. (Box 181, Folder 3039)
    - Interchurch World Movement of North America Reports, pamphlets, 1919-Jan 1920 (Box 181, Folder 3040)
    - Interchurch World Movement of May North America Reports, pamphlets 3041A International Missionary Council (see also: YDSL RG 31), 1920-1923 (Box 181, Folder 3041)
    - James Stokes Society Financial material, 1921-1948 (Box 181, Folder 3042)
    - James Stokes Society Financial material, 1949-1951 (Box 181, Folder 3043)
    - James Stokes Society Meeting minutes, 1921-1946 (Box 182, Folder 3044)
    - James Stokes Society Meeting minutes, 1947-1953 (Box 183, Folder 3045)
    - James Stokes Society Will of James Stokes, 1916 (Box 183, Folder 3046)
    - Laymen's Missionary Movement (see: YDSL HR1277)
    - Methodist Church, 1939 (Box 183, Folder 3047)
    - Orthodox Theological Seminary, 1933 (Box 183, Folder 3047)
    - Russian Student Christian Movement, 1923-1950 (Box 183, Folder 3047)
    - Russian Student Fund, 1941-1954 (Box 183, Folder 3048)
    - Student Volunteer Movement for Foreign Missions see also: (YDSL RG 42) (Box 183, Folder 3048A)
    - United War Work Campaign, Inc. 1918 (Box 183, Folder 3049)
    - United War Work Campaign, Inc., 1921 (Box 183, Folder 3050)
    - Washington Cathedral World Conference on Christian Life and Work, Oxford (World Conference on Church, Community, and State) (see:YDSL RG 62); YDSL World Conference on Faith and Order (see:YDSL RG 62); World Council of Churches (see: YDSL RG 500), 1924-1941, n.d. (Box 183, Folder 3051)
    - Yale Divinity School, c. 1909 (Box 183, Folder 3052)
    - YMCA-City General Secretaries' Association Conference, 1929 (Box 183, Folder 3053)
    - YMCA-General Board Meeting minutes, 1924-1929 (Box 183, Folder 3054)
    - YMCA-GeneraL Board Treasurer's Reports, 1929-1931 (Box 183, Folder 3055)
    - YMCA-General Board Treasurer's Reports, 1932-1933 (Box 183, Folder 3056)
    - YMCA-International Board MonthLy meeting minutes, 1937-1949 (Box 183, Folder 3057)
    - YMCA-International Board Policy Committee, 1939 (Box 183, Folder 3058)
    - YMCA-International Committee Auditor's reports, 1928, 1929 (Box 184, Folder 3059)
    - YMCA-International Committee Board of Trustees-annual meetings, 1929-1936 (Box 184, Folder 3060)
    - YMCA-International Committee Board of Trustees-annual meetings, 1930-1936 (Box 184, Folder 3061)
    - YMCA-International Comm-ittee Board of Trustees-annual meetings, 1938-1939 (Box 184, Folder 3062)
    - YMCA-International Comm-ittee Board of Trustees-annual meetings, 1940-1945 (Box 184, Folder 3063)
    - YMCA-International Committee Board of Trustees-By-Laws, Incorporation, 1930-1940 (Box 184, Folder 3064)
    - YMCA-International Committee Board of Trustees-Finanee Committee, 1931, 1939 (Box 184, Folder 3065)
    - YMCA-International Committee Board of Trustees-miscellaneous reports and minutes, 1928-1935 (Box 184, Folder 3066)
    - YMCA-International Comm-ittee Board of Trustees-Report of Controller, 1932-1942 (Box 184, Folder 3067)
    - YMCA-International Comm-ittee Board of Trustees-Report of President, 1936-1938 (Box 185, Folder 3068)
    - YMCA-International Committee Board of Trustees-Report of President, 1939-1942 (Box 185, Folder 3069)
    - YMCA-International Committee Board of Trustees-Report of President, 1943-1949 (Box 185, Folder 3070)
    - YMCA-International Committee Budgetary and financial matters, 1921-1933 (Box 185, Folder 3071)
    - YMCA-International Committee Committee on Properties and Trusts, 1933-1941 (Box 185, Folder 3072)
    - YMCA-International Committee Executive committee minutes, 1915-1932 (Box 185, Folder 3073)
    - YMCA-International Committee Executive committee minutes, 1932-1935 (Box 185, Folder 3074)
    - YMCA-International Committee Executive committee minutes, 1936-1941 (Box 186, Folder 3075)
    - YMCA-International Committee Executive committee-treasurer's reports, 1928-1932 (Box 186, Folder 3076)
    - YMCA-International Com-m-ittee Foreign Building Program IV, 1926 (Box 186, Folder 3077)
    - YMCA-International Committee Foreign Department Building Fund, 1916-1922 (Box 186, Folder 3078)
    - YMCA-International Committee Foreign Department-White House Conference, 1910 (Box 186, Folder 3079)
    - YMCA-International Committee Foreign Division Report, 1924 (Box 186, Folder 3080)
    - YMCA-International Committee Forward Program Fund, c. 1931 (Box 186, Folder 3081)
    - YMCA-International Committee General Secretaryship of J.R. Mott, 1912 (Box 186, Folder 3082)
    - YMCA-International Committee Incorporation, By-laws, 1915-1939 (Box 186, Folder 3083)
    - YMCA-International Committee Miscellaneous, 1897-1941 (Box 186, Folder 3084)
    - YMCA-International Committee Monthly meeting minutes, 1931-1932 (Box 186, Folder 3085)
    - YMCA-International Committee Monthly meeting minutes, 1933-1934 (Box 187, Folder 3086)
    - YMCA-International Committee Monthly meeting minutes, 1935-1936 (Box 187, Folder 3087)
    - YMCA-International Committee Plenary meeting, 1953 (Box 187, Folder 3088)
    - YMCA-International Committee Publicity reports, brochures, 1934, n.d. (Box 187, Folder 3089)
    - YMCA-International Committee Relationship to Eastern Orthodox Church (see World's Committee/World's Alliance) (Box 187)
    - YMCA-International Co i ttee Relationship to National Council, USA, 1923-1931 (Box 187, Folder 3090)
    - YMCA-International Committee Relationship to Roman Catholic Church, 1918-1927, n.d. (Box 187, Folder 3091)
    - YMCA-International Committee Source material on YMCA basis of membership, 1887-1906 (Box 187, Folder 3092)
    - YMCA-International Committee Source material on YMCA history, 1901-1905 (Box 187, Folder 3093)
    - YMCA-International Committee material on YMCA secretaryship, 1885-1909, n.d. (Box 187, Folder 3094)
    - YMCA-International Committee Treasurer's Reports, 1932-1933 (Box 188, Folder 3095)
    - YMCA-International Committee Trustees of the War Fund, 1920-1928 (Box 188, Folder 3096)
    - YMCA-International Committee Work in Balkans, 1921 (Box 188, Folder 3097)
    - YMCA-International Committee Work in China, c. 1901-1912, n.d. (Box 188, Folder 3098)
    - YMCA-International Committee Work in Europe-D.A. Davis reports, 1925, 1940 (Box 188, Folder 3099)
    - YMCA-International Committee Work in Greece, 1929 (Box 188, Folder 3100)
    - YMCA-International Committee Work in Japan (Box 188, Folder 3101)
    - YMCA-International Committee Work in Jerusalem, 1922-1933 (Box 188, Folder 3102)
    - YMCA-International Committee Work in Jerusalem, 1934-1935, n.d. (Box 188, Folder 3103)
    - YMCA-International Committee Treasurer's Reports, 1932-1933 (Box 188, Folder 3104)
    - YMCA-International Committee Work in Philippines, 1906-1907 (Box 188, Folder 3105)
    - YMCA-International Committee Work in Poland, 1920-1934 (Box 188, Folder 3106)
    - YMCA-International Committee Work in Poland, 1934-1938 (Box 188, Folder 3107)
    - YMCA-International Committee Work in Russia, 1916-1918 (Box 188, Folder 3108)
    - YMCA-International Committee Work in Russia, 1919-1924 (Box 188, Folder 3109)
    - YMCA-International Committee Work in Russia, 1926-1949, n.d. (Box 188, Folder 3110)
    - YMCA-International Committee Work in South America and the Caribbean, 1940-1941, n.d. (Box 188, Folder 3111)
    - YMCA-International Committee; Work in Sweden, 1945 (Box 188, Folder 3112)
    - Work in Turkey, n.d.
    - YMCA-International Convention of YMCAs of USA and Canada Detroit, 1919 (Box 188, Folder 3113)
    - Atlantic City, 1922
    - Washington, D.C., 1925
    - YMCA-International Convention of YMCAs of USA and Canada Cleveland, 1931 (Box 188, Folder 3114)
    - YMCA-International Convention of YMCAs of USA and Canada Cleveland, 1931 (Box 188, Folder 3115)
    - YMCA-International Convention of YMCAs of USA and Canada Niagara Falls, 1935 (Box 188, Folder 3116)
    - YMCA-National Board Board of Trustees, 1953-1954 (Box 188, Folder 3117)
    - YMCA-National Board Executive Committee minutes, 1940 (Box 188, Folder 3118)
    - YMCA-National Council, Canada Miscellaneous, 1911, 1928 (Box 188, Folder 3119)
    - YMCA-National Council, USA Annual meeting records, 1924-1939 (Box 189, Folder 3120)
    - YMCA-National Council, USA Army and Navy YMCAs (Box 189, Folder 3121)
    - YMCA-National Council, USA Budgets, reports, 1924-1925 (Box 189, Folder 3122)
    - YMCA-National Council, USA Budgets, reports, 1925-1926 (Box 190, Folder 3123)
    - YMCA-National Council, USA Budgets, reports, 1927 (Box 190, Folder 3124)
    - YMCA-National Council, USA Budgets, reports, 1928-1930 (Box 190, Folder 3125)
    - YMCA-National Council, USA Budgets, reports, 1930-1935 (Box 190, Folder 3126)
    - YMCA-National Council, USA Budgets, reports, 1936-1939 (Box 190, Folder 3127)
    - YMCA-National Council, USA Commission on Message and Purpose, 1930-1932, n.d. (Box 191, Folder 3128)
    - YMCA-National Council, USA Committee of Five to Study the 1927 Work of the National Council Member (Box 191, Folder 3129)
    - YMCA-National Council, USA Constitution and By-Laws, 1923 (Box 191, Folder 3130)
    - YMCA-National Council, USA Constitutional Convention, 1923 (Box 191, Folder 3131)
    - YMCA-National Council, USA Counselling Commission of the 1929 Churches (Box 191, Folder 3132)
    - YMCA-National Council, USA Foreign Division organization, 1924-1925, n.d. (Box 191, Folder 3133)
    - YMCA-National Council, USA General Secretaryship of J.R. Mott, 1922-1929 (Box 191, Folder 3134)
    - YMCA-National Council, USA General Secretary's Cabinet, 1926-1929 (Box 191, Folder 3135)
    - YMCA'National Council, USA Miscellaneous, 1929-1954, n.d. (Box 191, Folder 3136)
    - YMCA-National Councils, USA and Canada Committee-Joint Conference on National Policies, 1931 (Box 191, Folder 3137)
    - YMCA-National Councils, USA and Canada Foreign Committee publications, 1929-1939 (Box 191, Folder 3138)
    - YMCA-National Councils, USA and Canada Foreign Committee-Rehabilitation of work in Japan, 1923-1924 (Box 191, Folder 3139)
    - YMCA-National Councils, USA and Canada Foreign Committee-reports and brochures, 1931, n.d. (Box 191, Folder 3140)
    - YMCA-National Councils, USA and Canada Foreign Division Committee minutes, 1928-1931 (Box 191, Folder 3141)
    - YMCA-National Councils, USA and Canada Division Executive Committee minutes, 1929-1931 (Box 191, Folder 3142)
    - YMCA-National Councils, USA and Canada Material related to YMCA World Conference., 1937 (Box 191, Folder 3143)
    - YMCA-National Councils, USA and Canada Relationships, 1923-1935 (Box 191, Folder 3144)
    - YMCA-National War Work Council Criticisms: Baptist, 1919 (Box 192, Folder 3145)
    - YMCA-National War Work Council Criticisms: Government investigation, 1920-1923 (Box 192, Folder 3146)
    - YMCA-National War Work Council Criticisms: Miscellaneous, 1919-1920 (Box 192, Folder 3147)
    - YMCA-National War Work Council Documentary pamphlets and articles, 1917-1919, n.d. (Box 192, Folder 3148)
    - YMCA-National War Work Council Financial Appeals and records, 1917 (Box 192, Folder 3149)
    - YMCA-National War Work Council Financial appeals and records, 1918 (Box 192, Folder 3150)
    - YMCA-National War Work Council Financial appeals and records, 1919, 1920 (Box 192, Folder 3151)
    - YMCA-National War Work Council Financial appeals and records, 1921-1927 (Box 192, Folder 3152)
    - YMCA-National War Work Council General reports, minutes, 1917-1920 (Box 192, Folder 3153)
    - YMCA-National War Work Council Work in Russia Work in Poland (OVERSIZE), 1921 (Box 192, Folder 3154)
    - YMCA-World's Committee/World's Alliance Conferences-miscellaneous, 1928-1939 (Box 192, Folder 3155)
    - YMCA-World's Committee/World's Alliance Conferences-miscellaneous, 1933-1939 (Box 193, Folder 3156)
    - YMCA-World's Committee/worlds Alliance Conferences-miscellaneous, 1942-1946, n.d. (Box 193, Folder 3157)
    - YMCA-World's Committee/World's Alliance Constitutions, Directories, 1913-1947 (Box 193, Folder 3158)
    - YMCA-World's Committee/worlds Alliance Executive Committee, 1927-1930 (Box 193, Folder 3159)
    - YMCA-World's Committee/world's Alliance Executive Committee, 1931-1938 (Box 193, Folder 3160)
    - YMCA-World's Committee/World's Alliance Executive Committee, 1939 (Box 193, Folder 3161)
    - YMCA-World's Committee/World's Alliance Executive Committee, 1946-1951 (Box 193, Folder 3162)
    - YMCA-Worlds Committee/world's Alliance; Geneva Headquarters Building Project, 1949 (Box 194, Folder 3163)